My Resume



Kallirroi Zarkadoula

- $\bullet \quad kallirroi.zarkadoula@gmail.com$
- kzarkadoula.myportfolio.com/
- kallirroi-zarkadoula

Languages

- English (Proficient)
- French (Proficient)

Interests

- Contemporary Dance
- Ballet
- Classical Piano

Career Profile (Download CV as PDF)

Graduate student of Electrical and Computer Engineering Department with communication skills and work experience as Quality Assurance Engineer pursuing my Masters in Human-Computer Interaction. My research via my thesis focused on hardware acceleration for Deep Neural Networks on FPGA using Tensorflow for the verification of the results. During my master, I focus my coursework on interaction design, UX design and prototyping.

Education

MSc in Human-Computer Interaction

2019 - Present

University of Patras

Modules studied include:

- Computer Graphics and Virtual Reality
- Interactive Technologies
- Software Quality

Thesis title:

• Effectiveness of serious game designs for software developers supervised by Professor Michalis Xenos

MEng in Electrical and Computer Engineering

2012 - 2019

University of Patras

Modules studied include:

- Artificial Intelligence
- Speech and Natural Language Recognition
- Estimation Theory and Stochastic Control

Thesis Title:

• "Hardware Design for Deep Learning" supervised by Associate Professor Vassilis Paliouras

Experiences

Grader

04/2020 - 06/2020

Interactive Technologies Laboratory, Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, University of Patras, Patras

• Grading of the laboratory exercises of Procedural Programming course.

Quality Assurance Engineer

08/2018 - 12/2019

Pobuca - Sieben, Patras

- Recommending interfaces that the user will find usable and efficient
- Working as part of a team to achieve our common targets and ensure our tasks were finished in time
- Tasked with manual execution of tests in web, ios and android platforms
- Discovering bugs of the product and suggesting solutions-improvements
- Developing performance and stress testing
- Maintaining and creating software automated tests
- Ensuring that software is aligned with product's standards
- Monitoring development process and setting requirements

Quality Assurance Engineer intern

05/2018 - 07/2019

Pobuca - Sieben, Patras

- Entrusted with maintenance of automated tests and creation of new ones
- Took charge of complex problem solving
- Developed and wrote test scenarios

Skills & Proficiency

Python & Django

 ${\bf Javascript}$

 ${\rm HTML5/CSS/Bootstrap}$

C/C#

Adobe Suite

Selenium/Puppeteer/Cypress

 ${\bf OpenCV/TensorFlow/Unity}$